User reviews
	
Anjali Verma
26 March 2019
please update trip to show distance traveled correct upto at least two decimal places, for exact calculation in distance traveled for competitors in running.
	
nic patel
4 April 2019
very useful nic app
	
vaibhav patel
1 April 2017
1
the best ever App!! works 100%...
	
Ray Tannous
21 September 2016
5
Freezes if no GPS No landscape. Unable to stop.
	
paul fox
6 September 2016
2
Max speed is inaccurate: it seems to be an average of previoius max speeds, or something like that. That makes me question the accuracy of everything else the app reports. Not being able stop and restart without having all the values reset is a problem too -- it would be nice to be able to stop
	
Sam H
3 August 2016
3
beautiful display, not correct distance and time are correct, but MPH and max speed are suspect. I've never walked 48 mph before, though it's still a stretch goal of mine.
	
Christina Widder
27 July 2016
2
Accurate This app works great. Works 100% true
	
Antony C. F.
19 July 2016
2
A very useful app.
	
Michael Clausen
7 July 2016
2
Good app, but.... Great app, but the acceleration needs to be more fluid.... I shouldn't have to hold my speed steady for 5sec before it changes on the app...
	
Jay G
5 July 2016
2
It's ok Not bad, but it needs to be able to control the phone standby.
	
Hemat Chauhan
27 June 2016
3
Wery nice app
	
Gopi Sanghani
20 July 2016
1
Accurate & Speedy
	
Nikhil Kumar
20 March 2017
Kahan padta hai ye Darshan Institute of engineering 😂😂😂
	
გიორგი ხულორდავა
21 June 2016
Fantasticus 😉
	
Pritesh Ramani
8 May 2017
Most most accurate app
	
Ionuț Vali
18 July 2016
Simple and effective. Gr8 job.
	
Neelesh Kumar
19 June 2016
Fantastico
	
chintan kanani
3 May 2016
2
Nice app...
	
Dipak Ramoliya
3 May 2016
3
Excellent